SHAIKH MOHAMMAD AAMIR MOHIB Mobile number: +91-8767938959 Email Id: kaaamirz98@gmail.com

Add: 154/B4, BMC building, Room No. 1, Near Jama Masjid, Dharavi Main Road, Mumbai- 400017

Personal Details

Date of Birth: 8th Feb 1994

Gender: Male

Marital Status: Single

Languages Known: English, Hindi & Urdu (Read, Write, Speak)

• Nationality: Indian

Hobbies: Gaming, Cricket, Swimming, Riding, Singing, Dancing, Trekking, Hiking, Traveling

• Skills: Team Work, Good planner, Good Communication Skills, Active Listener, Adaptability.

Education Qualification

| Sr. No. | Examination | Board | Year of Passing | Percentage | Class |
|---------|------------------------------|-------------------|-----------------|------------|-----------|
| 1 | BSC (Information Technology) | Mumbai University | 2018 | 5.3 | 2nd Class |
| 2 | HSC | Maharashtra Board | 2012 | 63 | 1st Class |
| 3 | SSC | Maharashtra Board | 2010 | 62 | 1st Class |

Institute Attended

- Rizvi College of Arts, Science & Commerce, 2015-18
- M. H. Saboo Siddik College of Engineering, 2010-12
- Our Lady School, till 2010

Career Objective

"To secure a challenging position in an organization wherein I can leverage customer relationship building skills combined with years of sales experience in corporate goods market."

Professional Summary

Experience of almost 3 years in Sales & Marketing in areas of generating leads, cold calls/visits. Understanding client requirement & sharing the quotations to close the deal. Customization as per client budgets.

Key Professional Skills

Sales & Marketing
Communication Skills
Perseverance
Business Development
Interpersonal Skills
Analytical
Self-Motivation
Time Management
Ability to Work under Pressure
Decision Making
Creative
Negotiation

Work Experience

1) Currently working with Oravel Stay Pvt Ltd. (OYO)

(August 2019 - Till Date)

Designation: Demand Manager

- Approaching New Clients.
- Arranging and attending meetings.
- Making 'pitches', to win new business for the firm.
- Approaching New clients & Existing clients to generate business.
- Generate lead by Cold Calls & Cold visits
- Working with Corporate & Government Organizations.
- Close deals for stay solutions & for events across place.
- Meeting and liaising with clients to discuss and identify their stay requirements.
- Co-ordination with internal team to share valued deals for clients as per their requirements.
- Negotiating with clients for their Quarterly, Yearly packages.
- Ensuring that communication flows to be effective.
- Handling budgets, managing comfort stay and invoicing the clients.
- Working with travelling agencies colleagues to devise the stay requirements which meet the client's brief and budget.
- Acting as the link between the client and the travelling agency by maintaining regular contact with both.
- Monitoring the effectiveness of stay with all amenities and matching up to the client requirement.
- Servicing the client throughout from booking till the execution and further follow up & Billing.
- Clients serviced like DDB Mundra, Hexagon Nutrition, Borosil Glass, Yash Raj Films, Ultra Media, Gunnebo India, Golds Gym etc.

2) Worked with Network Techlab

(July 2018 - August 2019)

Designation: Business Development Executives

- To Generate lead by Cold Calling/ Cold Visits
- Pitch company details with New & Existing Clients
- Close deals & follow ups
- Recurring business from current organizations
- Create a funnel to keep a track on Monthly basis business records

3) Worked with Alshafi International Agency

(June 2013 - Sept 2014)

Designation: Telesales Executives

Company Summary -

Oyo Rooms (stylized as **OYO**), also known as **Oyo Homes & Hotels**, is an Indian hotel chain. It is the world's third-larges and fastest-growing hospitality chain of leased and franchised hotels, homes and living spaces. It focus on budgeted hotels.

Computer Skills

Knowledge of Microsoft Office.

Declaration-

I hereby declare that the information given above is true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Place: Mumbai